OLADIPO BUSAYO DANIEL

House 7, Omigade Street, Ogooluwa Osogbo, Osun State, Nigeria.

+(234) 8160230048, 8056737098

busayomi1300@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A highly motivated, hardworking and detailed individual, with a passion for tech. I am knowledgeable about information technology as it evolve globally. I am a reliable person with strong communication and teamwork spirit. Proficient in data entry, record keeping, statistical analysis, research and problemsolving.

SKILLS

- ✓ Sound Knowledge of Windows and Linux Operating System
- ✓ Technical Support.
- ✓ Website Development (WordPress, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Python)
- ✓ Microsoft Office Suite(Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Google docs).
- ✓ Writer (Content Creation, Article, Blog Post, Business Plan, Financial Projections Technical Report Writing etc.)
- ✓ Team Management.

EDUCATION

Osun State University, Osogbo Main Campus, Osogbo Osun State. (BSc Computer Science) 2018-2022

Osun State College of Technology, Esa-Oke, Osun State. (Diploma Computer Science) 2014-2016

WORK HISTORY

IT Support Officer – 09/2021 till Present.

DVS Reliable Energy Limited, Osogbo., Osun State.

- Responsible for maintaining, securing, and troubleshooting an organization's computer network. Installs and configures network hardware and software, monitors performance, and implements security measures.
- 2. Oversee and manage multiple programs within an organization. Develop program strategies, lead project teams, manage budgets, assess risks, and communicate with stakeholders.
- 3. Impart knowledge and skills related to information technology and computer systems. Design and conduct training sessions, provide technical support, and assess training needs.
- 4. Manage digital marketing campaigns across platforms. Analyze marketing data, coordinate logistics operations, and lead a team of marketing and logistics professionals.

Technical Support Officer 1 – 10/2019 to 09/2021. **KINT-BAZ Global Resources,** Osogbo., Osun State.

- 1. Assist and support customers via phone, email, or chat., address inquiries and resolve issues promptly.

 Troubleshoot technical problems and escalate when needed. Maintain accurate customer records. Collaborate with other teams for customer satisfaction.
- 2. Install, configure, and maintain computer systems and networks. Monitor system performance and security. Troubleshoot hardware and software issues. Manage user accounts and access permissions. Implement data backups and disaster recovery.
- 3. Analyze and document business requirements. Design effective IT solutions. Conduct feasibility studies and costbenefit analyses. Create detailed system specifications. Support implementation and system optimization.
- **4.** Collect, clean, and organize data. Apply statistical techniques for analysis. Create reports and visualizations. Identify patterns and insights. Provide data-driven recommendations.

Technical Officer – 11/2016 to 10/2018.

Joint Admission Matriculation Board (JAMB) ICT Center., Block Y (Commercial) OSPDC Service area, Agunbelewo-Ilobu road, Osogbo, Osun State.

1. Computer Network Administrator 2, Social Media Management, Computer Hardware and Software Engineering/Maintenance, Online Registrations.